zvents.com 2014-10-26

# Privacy Policy - Zvents

Updated Effective: January 10, 2013

Zvents, Inc. (Zvents) provides a collection of online resources, including advertising, event calendaring, email services, links to third party sites and other features and services, available at our website located at [http://www.zvents.com](http://www.zvents.com/) (collectively, the "Service"). 

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, store, and protect your personal information in connection with providing the Services. By using or accessing any part of the Service, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy and all other policies or notices posted by us on our website. 

Throughout this Privacy Policy, we use the term “personal information” to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous or aggregated so that it can no longer be used, whether in combination with other information or otherwise, to identify a specific person. 

Zvents, Inc. is a wholly owned subsidiary of StubHub Inc., and is part of the eBay Inc. corporate family. 

eBay Inc. has established a set of corporate rules for privacy, known as Binding Corporate Rules (BCRs), which are our global privacy standards for all eBay Inc. companies. These BCRs have been approved by a number of European Union privacy regulators. They are a commitment by eBay Inc. to protect your personal information and honor our privacy obligations regardless of where your personal information is collected, processed or stored. Depending on where you reside, the BCRs may also provide you some additional privacy rights through your local privacy regulator or court. More information about eBay Inc’s BCRs and its global privacy practices, principles is available at the [eBay Privacy Center](http://www.ebayprivacycenter.com/). 

You can browse the site and perform a Zvents search without giving us any personal information. 

Zvents collects a limited amount of information your browser makes available whenever you visit the website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services. 

Some of our Services require you to register for an account. Zvents asks you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address, zip code, and a password for your account) and we will use that information to provide the service. 

When we require personal information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us. 

When you create an event, venue, or group, post comments or photos, that content becomes public. The public will see any information that you include in your content, and as such, Zvents has no control over how this information will be used. For that reason, please think carefully about what personal information you disclose in your content. 

We also collect anonymous information, such as your IP address, the type of browser you use, the pages on our site that you visit, the search terms that you enter and the advertisements that you click. This information is used to provide features and help us diagnose problems, administer the site and otherwise improve our service to you. 

We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which Zvents Inc. or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country. 

You can access and change your account information by logging into your account and accessing your MyZvents profile. 

Zvents uses cookies to track specific user sessions on the web site. This lets us provide user-specific functionality without asking you to re-enter your user name on every single page. Our cookies contain only a small, anonymous piece of identifying information called a session id (like a random number) that we map back to your account while you are on the site. Our cookies contain no other personal information. 

We do not rent or sell your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your express consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. 

We may also share your personal information with [Members of the eBay Inc. corporate family](http://www.ebayprivacycenter.com/about-us/corporate-family) to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, services and communications. Members of our corporate family will send you marketing communications based on this information but only if you've requested their services. 

We will only disclose your personal information to third parties if we are required to do so by law or have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Zvents, its users or the public. 

In the event of a transfer of ownership of Zvents Inc., such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is 14transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share aggregated information with others. Examples of this include the number of users who searched for "San Francisco Giants" or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. This aggregated information contains nothing that is personally traceable to you. 

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect is accurate and up to date, and delete any information that is no longer useful or relevant to our operations. We retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigation, enforce our User Agreement and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. 

This web site may contain links to websites not owned or operated by Zvents. Please be aware that Zvents is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by Zvents' services are developed by people over whom Zvents exercises no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information. 

Zvents may present links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed. We use this information to understand and improve the quality of Zvents' search technology. For instance, this data helps us determine how often users are satisfied with the first result of a query and how often they proceed to later results. 

Please note this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will always announce any change in advance. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices you can contact us.
